Finding Aid for Donald S. Leonard Papers 1925-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Civil Defense
  - Post-World War II 1947-1952
    - Regional Civil Defense Cooperation 1947-1952
      - Midwestern Conference of State Civil Defense Directors (Box 9)
      - Council of State Governments Civil Defense Conference (Box 9)
      - State Civil Defense publications and plans
        - Florida (Box 9)
        - Indiana (Box 9)
        - Nevada (Box 9)
        - New Hampshire (Box 9)
        - New Jersey (Box 9)
        - New York (Box 9)
        - North Carolina (Box 9)
        - Ohio (Box 9)
        - Miscellanea (Box 9)
    - Mock Nuclear Attack Exercises 1950
      - Seattle
        - Notes and correspondence (Box 9)
        - Agendas and general documents (Box 9)
        - Reports of city departments (Box 9)
        - Transcript of critique, 5 folders (Box 9)
      - Chicago
        - Correspondence and agendas, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Statement of Problem and Responses, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - City Department Civil Defense Plans, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Washington-miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Michigan Civil Defense
      - Office of Director of Civil Defense 1947-1952
        - Organizational charts (Box 10)
        - MOCD newsletter 1951-1952 (Box 10)
        - Civil Defense information kit (Box 10)
        - Personnel lists (Box 10)
        - Michigan Plan for Civil Defense
          - Drafts and correspondence (Box 10)
          - Police Services appendix (Box 10)
          - Final Plan (Box 10)
        - Plan for Control Centers (Box 10)
        - Civil Defense Recommendations by S.L.A. Marshall (Box 10)
        - Budget (Box 10)
        - Meetings 1949-April 1952, 7 folders (Box 10)
          (agendas, notes, minutes)
        - Correspondence (Box 10)
        - Memos, notes, form letters (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous reports and memos (Box 10)
        - General orders, bulletins, informational letters, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Suggested legislation
          - Subversive control 1948 (Box 10)
          - New Civil Defense Act 1951-1952 (Box 10)
          - Lists of Michigan Communities (Box 10)
      - Local Civil Defense Organization 1947-1952
        - Personnel (Box 10)
        - Mutual Aid Areas (Box 10)
        - Progress reports-Wayne County outside Detroit, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Progress reports-Macomb, Monroe, Oakland, St. Clair, Washtenaw counties (Box 10)
        - Progress reports-Critical Communities outside Detroit Metropolitan area, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Detroit Civil Defense Planning 1947-1952
        - Correspondence (Box 10)
        - Police Civil Defense Plan (Box 10)
        - Emergency Police Reserve Training Manual (Box 10)
        - Civil Defense Digest by Detroit Public Library (Box 10)
      - Mock Nuclear Attack Exercises 1951
        - Sault Ste. Marie
          - Correspondence and memos (Box 11)
          - Reports and observations (Box 11)
        - Detroit
          - Agendas and remarks (Box 11)
          - State Police reports (Box 11)
          - City department reports, 6 folders (Box 11)
      - Ground Observer Corps 1949-1952
        - Organization (Box 11)
        - Conference on Expansion of Aircraft Warning System, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Correspondence (Box 11)
        - Notes (Box 11)
        - Progress reports (Box 11)
        - Observation Posts
          - Lists (Box 11)
          - Correspondence July-December 1950, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Grand Rapids Filter Center (Box 11)
        - Report-Notes on Ground Observer Corps and Civil Air Raid Warning (Box 11)
      - Air Raid Warning System 1950-1952
        - Correspondence and reports (Box 11)
        - Revision of Air Raid Warning Signals (Box 11)
      - Special Aspects of Civil Defense 1947-1952
        - Air Raid Shelters (Box 11)
        - Auxiliary police training course (Box 11)
        - Civil Air Patrol (Box 11)
        - Communications engineering (Box 11)
        - Emergency procurement of blood, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Evacuation policy (Box 11)
        - Fire protection (Box 11)
        - Highway and traffic control (Box 11)
        - Medical, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Public works (Box 11)
        - Radiological monitoring (Box 11)
        - Red Cross (Box 11)
        - School and Civil Defense (Box 11)
        - State-owned fire trucks-Survey, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
      - Printed material regarding civil defense during World War II era 1941-1948 (Box 12)
      - Printed material regarding civil defense after World War II 1947-1952 (Box 13)
      - Clippings pertaining to Civil Defense undated, 1941-1953, 12 folders (Box 13)
- Michigan State Police 1929-1952
  The Michigan State Police series is divided into organizational and subject areas. These papers are more closely tied to Leonard's career than are the civil defense papers, and cover primarily the activities of the second district (Detroit) up to 1945, and the state headquarters in Lansing from 1945 to 1952. Here again the collection includes some of the files of Leonard's predecessor as commissioner, Oscar Olander. These files contain documentation on the murder of State Senator William G. Hooper, the attempted assassinations of Walter and Victor Reuther, and state police involvement in strikes and other labor disturbances.
  - General
    - General-Publicity (Box 14)
    - Rules and regulations (Box 14)
    - Inter-office correspondence 1938-1952, 12 folders (Box 14)
    - Headquarters staff meetings 1947-1951 (Box 14)
  - District and Post Commanders Files
    - District Commanders' Meetings
      - Agendas and related material 1946-1951 (Box 14)
      - Minutes 1947 (Box 14)
      - Minutes 1948-1951 (Box 14)
    - Post Commanders' Meetings
      - First District 1947 (Box 14)
      - Second District 1937-1948, 4 folders (Box 14)
      - Third District 1949-1951 (Box 14)
      - Fourth District 1946-1950 (Box 14)
      - Fifth District 1942-1950 (Box 14)
      - Seventh District 1947-1952 (Box 14)
      - Eighth District 1946-1950 (Box 14)
  - Divisions
    - Uniform Division
      - Statistics 1940-1949 (Box 14)
      - Police vehicles (Box 14)
      - Police aircraft (Box 14)
    - Communications Bureau
      - General (Box 14)
      - Communication manual (Box 14)
    - Fire Bureau
      - General (Box 14)
      - Standards for Homes for Aged (Box 14)
      - Liquefied Petroleum Gas Regulation (Box 14)
    - Traffic Bureau-General (Box 14)
    - Detective Division
      - Memos 1946-1947, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Operations Office
      - Memos (Box 14)
      - Record of Politicians' Transportation requests January-February 1950 (Box 14)
    - Recruit Training School
      - Course materials, 7 folders (Box 14)
      - Course materials, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Schedules and curriculum (Box 15)
      - Examinations, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Graduation exercises (Box 15)
  - Administration
    - General
      - Governor's staff meetings (Box 15)
        - January 1949 (Box 15)
        - July 1949 (Box 15)
        - October 1949 (Box 15)
      - Building Program (Box 15)
    - Personnel
      - Investigation of applicants (Box 15)
      - Veteran compensation under GI Bill of Rights (Box 15)
      - Promotion procedures (Box 15)
      - Budget requests and reports, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Meeting of promoted or transferred personnel (Box 15)
      - Salary material, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Trial boards (Box 15)
      - Insurance, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Personnel distribution (Box 15)
      - lists of enlisted positions (Box 15)
      - Personnel lists 1945-1947 (Box 15)
      - Personnel lists 1950-1953 (Box 15)
    - Reorganization
      - Papers 1947-1948 (Box 15)
      - Papers 1950-1952 (Box 15)
    - Special Details, Events, Conferences
      - General Motors Plant Police Chiefs' meeting 1940 (Box 15)
      - Fourth Army Orientation Course 1943 (Box 15)
      - Military Police Detail 1944 (Box 15)
      - Conference on Chemical Tests for Intoxication 1946 (Box 15)
      - Assignment of Police Commissioner for Japan 1946-1949
        - Correspondence (Box 15)
        - General (Box 15)
      - Governor's Inauguration 1947 (Box 15)
      - Air Force Operation-Eglin A.F.B. 1948 (Box 15)
      - Governor's aide 1948-1949 (Box 15)
      - Election recount 1950, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Governor's Inauguration 1951 (Box 15)
      - Governor's Law Enforcement meeting 1951 (Box 15)
      - Michigan Highway Safety Seminar 1952 (Box 15)
    - Legislation and Procedures
      - Cap Pistols (Box 16)
        - Correspondence (Box 16)
        - Clippings (Box 16)
      - Firearms Laws (Box 16)
      - Liquor Control Commission (Box 16)
      - Mobilization Plans (Box 16)
      - One Man Grand Jury (Box 16)
    - Command Officers' School
      - Course Material
        - 1949 (Box 16)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 16)
      - Speech (Box 16)
    - Military Police School
      - Control of Civil Disturbances 1948-1949 (Box 16)
    - Refresher School
      - Course material, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - School for newly elected sheriffs
      - Course material (Box 16)
    - Bulletins and Orders
      - Drafts and suggestions (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous 1940-1946 (Box 16)
      - Bulletins 1947-1952 (Box 16)
      - General orders 1947-1952 (Box 16)
      - Special orders 1947-1952 (Box 16)
      - Uniform Division bulletins undated, 1946 (Box 16)
      - Uniform Division bulletins 1947-1951 (Box 16)
    - Press releases 1947-1952, 9 folders (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Michigan Dept. of Aeronautics 1946-1949 (Box 17)
    - Capital punishment
      - Correspondence and notes 1929-1931 (Box 17)
      - Clippings 1929-1947 (Box 17)
    - Wisconsin State Police 1946-1948 (Box 17)
    - Kefauver Committee 1951 (Box 17)
    - Rulings on Attorney General 1943-1947 (Box 17)
    - Departmental citation 1949 (Box 17)
    - Report-Prevalent types of confidence games by Edward Cooper 1947 (Box 17)
    - Manual for policewomen 1945 (Box 17)
    - Fraudulent diversion of automobiles 1950 (Box 17)
    - Proposed book: Crimes, cops, and clues by Victor Beck 1948 (Box 17)
    - Walter Reuther-Permission to have armored vehicle 1949 (Box 17)
    - Alleged kidnapping of prisoner by Donald Leonard 1938 (Box 17)
    - Driving of state legislators 1949 (Box 17)
    - Ingham County Grand Jury 1946-1948, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Alleged corruption Flint Police Department 1947 (Box 17)
    - State Police Medical Advisor (Dr. LeMoyne Snyder) 1939-1948, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Miscellanea, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Notes (Box 17)
  - Case Files
    - Prostitution (Box 17)
    - Liquor (Box 17)
    - Gambling
      - General, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - First District (Box 17)
      - Second District, 5 folders (Box 17)
      - Third District (Box 17)
      - Seventh District, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - William G. Hooper Murder
      - General 1945-1951, 7 folders (Box 18)
      - Statements and depositions, 8 folders (Box 18)
      - Clippings (Box 18)
      - Miscellanea (Box 18)
    - Walter Reuther shooting 1948-1954, 6 folders (Box 18)
    - Victor Reuther shooting 1949 (Box 18)
    - Walter and Victor Reuther shootings-clippings, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Lydia Thompson murder 1945-1950 (Box 18)
    - Strikes-Policy
      - Undated (Box 18)
      - 1932-1939 (Box 18)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 18)
      - 1947-1949 (Box 18)
    - Strikes-Individual strikes
      - Aero-Quip Co., Jackson 1948 (Box 19)
      - Briggs 1945 (Box 19)
      - Chrysler 1948 (Box 19)
      - General Motors 1945 (Box 19)
      - Marquette County Iron Mines 1946 (Box 19)
      - Michigan Bell Telephone Co. 1947 (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
      - Mt. Clemens Pottery 1941 (Box 19)
      - Railroads 1946 (Box 19)
      - Remington Rand, Benton Harbor 1947
        - General, 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Congressional inquiry into strike, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Shakespeare Co., Kalamazoo 1948, 4 folders (Box 19)
      - United Auto Workers-General (Box 19)
    - Jackson State Prison Investigation 1947
      - Summary of witnesses and investigation (Box 19)
      - Testimony, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Prison industries (Box 19)
      - Prison administration (Box 19)
      - Pardon and parole board (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea, 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Jackson State Prison Riot 1952
      - Summary of events (Box 19)
      - Operations reports, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Pontiac State Hospital Investigation 1947 (Box 19)
  - Clippings concerning Michigan State Police
    - Gambling 1934-1946 (Box 19)
    - Graft in Macomb County 1946-1947 (Box 19)
    - Communism 1946-1947, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Oscar Olander Retirement 1947 (Box 19)
    - General undated, 1942-1947, 8 folders (Box 19)
    - General 1947-1952, 11 folders (Box 20)
- Detroit Police Department 1952-1954
  The Detroit Police Department series contains Leonard's personal files as commissioners. The files have been arranged by subject.
  - Topical File
    - Arrest records, access to (Box 20)
    - Automobile operator licensing (Box 20)
    - Awards (Box 20)
    - Call boxes (Box 20)
    - Citizens' complaints (Box 20)
    - Civil Defense Ordinance, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Communism
      - Rosenberg Clemency Committee (Box 20)
      - Board of Education (Box 20)
      - General correspondence (Box 20)
    - Court dispositions (Box 20)
    - Data processing in robbery analysis (Box 20)
    - Detective School (Box 20)
    - Detroit Police Officers' Association, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Disaster plan (Box 20)
    - Disasters
      - Port Huron tornado 1953 (Box 20)
      - Flint tornado 1953, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Disciplinary cases (Box 20)
    - Furloughs and annual leave (Box 20)
    - Gambling-Bingo (Box 20)
    - General orders (Box 20)
    - Gillespie, Joann-Murder (Box 20)
    - Graft investigation (Box 20)
    - Historical material (Box 20)
    - Information manual 1949 (Box 20)
    - Juke boxes (Box 20)
    - Labor (Box 20)
    - Lieutenants and Sergeants Association (Box 20)
    - Meetings (Box 20)
    - Memos, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Merit System (Box 20)
    - Military personnel, arrest of (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Narcotic (Box 20)
    - Notations (Box 20)
    - Operation Fingerprint (Box 20)
    - Personnel-Hiring of 19 year olds (Box 20)
    - Police Academy course materials (Box 20)
    - Police cadets (Box 20)
    - Presidential inauguration 1953 (Box 20)
    - Racial
      - Gang activities and complaints (Box 20)
      - Mayors Interracial Committee-Report (Box 21)
      - Catillian Club (Box 21)
      - Urban League (Box 21)
    - Radio in police work (Box 21)
    - Retirement (Box 21)
    - Scout car run sheets (Box 21)
    - Sergeants and Lieutenants Command School (Box 21)
    - Service ratings (Box 21)
    - Sex crimes (Box 21)
    - Sick leave report (Box 21)
    - Six day work week (Box 21)
    - Skid Row (Box 21)
    - Special orders (Box 21)
    - Special orders (Box 21)
    - Weapons (Box 21)
    - Walter Winchell allegations of communism in DPD (Box 21)
    - Woman's Division (Box 21)
    - Youth Bureau (Box 21)
  - Clippings
    - Bingo, 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Communism, 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Juke Box investigation (Box 21)
    - Murder of Joann Gillespie (Box 21)
    - Police looting after tornado (Box 21)
    - Police numbers racket investigation (Box 21)
    - Tornadoes (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
- Political Files
  The Political Files consists of correspondence, speech material, issue files, campaign plans, and other campaign materials for the gubernatorial elections of 1952, 1954, and 1956.
  - Election of 1950 (Governor)
    - General (Box 22)
  - Election of 1952 (Governor)
    - Mailing lists, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Register of incoming mail (Box 22)
    - Correspondence undated, February 1952-August, 1952, 15 folders (Box 22)
    - Form letters (Box 22)
    - Press releases, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Chronology and schedules January 1952-August 1952, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Nomination petition summary (Box 22)
    - Pre-election survey (Box 22)
    - Newspaper advertising summary (Box 22)
    - Campaign publications, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Contributors (Box 22)
    - Campaign issues (Box 22)
    - Campaign organization by county (Box 22)
    - Primary election results (Box 22)
    - Republican State Convention (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Clippings (Box 22)
  - Election of 1954 (Governor)
    - Announcement of candidacy (Box 22)
    - Mailing lists, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Campaign organization chairmen, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Campaign volunteers, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Form letters, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - County correspondence files (Box 23)
      (arranged alphabetically by name of county)
      - Alcona-Manistee, 54 folders (Box 23)
      - Marquette-Wayne (A-G), 43 folders (Box 24)
      - Wayne (H-Z), 19 folders (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Out-of-state May 1954-November 1954, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Telegrams (Box 25)
    - Incoming correspondence register (Box 25)
    - Campaign schedule (Box 25)
    - Press releases Undated, March 1954-October 1954, 5 folders (Box 25)
    - Campaign Employee Files
      - Dean, Merritt (Box 25)
      - Emmons, Harold (Box 25)
      - Loomis, Pat (Box 25)
      - Tumas, Edward (Box 25)
      - Zarry, George (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Campaign Issues
      - Agriculture (Box 26)
      - Conservation (Box 26)
      - Democrats (Box 26)
      - F.E.P.C. (Box 26)
      - F.H.A. (Box 26)
      - Four Year Term (Box 26)
      - Franchise (Box 26)
      - Highways, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Insurance Scandal (Box 26)
      - Judiciary (Box 26)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 26)
      - Labor (Box 26)
      - Mental Health (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - New York Trip materials (Box 26)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 26)
      - Platform (Box 26)
      - Police numbers probe (Box 26)
      - Reorganization of State Government (Box 26)
      - Republican Speakers' Card Kit (Box 26)
      - Republicans, National (Box 26)
      - Republicans, State (Box 26)
      - Social Security (Box 26)
      - Taxation (Box 26)
      - Trucks (Box 26)
      - Unemployment Compensation (Box 26)
      - Upper Peninsula (Box 26)
      - Veterans (Box 26)
      - Water Resources (Box 26)
      - Wayne University (Box 26)
      - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 26)
      - Workmen's Compensation (Box 26)
    - Republican State Convention, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Campaign statistics (Box 26)
    - Public Relations Program
      - Suggested programs (Box 26)
      - Correspondence and memos, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Television
        - Schedule (Box 26)
        - Budget (Box 26)
        - Questions (Box 26)
        - Scripts, 6 folders (Box 26)
      - Radio (Box 26)
      - Printed materials, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Magazine articles (Box 27)
    - Leonard for Governor newsletter (Box 27)
    - Michigan G.O.P. newsletter (Box 27)
    - Clippings, 6 folders (Box 27)
    - Homer Ferguson senatorial campaign materials, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Election of 1956 (Governor)
    - County organization (Box 27)
    - Correspondence November 1954-June 1956, 6 folders (Box 27)
    - Form letters (Box 27)
    - Petition summaries (Box 27)
    - Campaign schedules (Box 27)
    - Press releases (Box 27)
    - Campaign issues (Box 27)
    - Albert Cobo (Box 27)
    - Public Relations (Box 27)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Wayne County Republican Committee (Box 27)
    - Republican State Convention 1955 (Box 27)
    - U.S. Senate Republican memo, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Republican Legislative Campaign Kit (Box 27)
    - "Fundamental of Campaign Organization" by Murray Chotiner (Box 27)
    - Miscellanea (Box 27)
    - Clippings (Box 27)
- Organization and Activities Files
  The Organization and Activities series is arranged by name of organization and contains combinations of official files of Leonard as an organizational officer and personal files of Leonard as active member of these organizations. The most extensive of these files relate to the International Association of Chiefs of Police (1932-1966), the Michigan Association of Chiefs of Police (1928-1966), the Associated Police Communications Officers (1935-1950), the Permanent Legislative Committee (1944-1963), the State Liquor Control Commission (1961-1966), the Citizens' Advisory Committee on Equal Educational Opportunities (1961-1962), and the Michigan Bar Association (1956-1966).
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police 1932-1966
    - Constitution (Box 28)
    - Correspondence
      - 1940 re firearms legislation (Box 28)
      - 1941 (Box 28)
      - 1949 (Box 28)
      - 1950 (Box 28)
      - 1953 re IACP convention planning (Box 28)
      - 1958-1960 (Box 28)
      - 1962 (Box 28)
      - 1963 (Box 28)
      - 1964 (Box 28)
      - 1965 (Box 28)
      - 1966 (Box 28)
    - Conventions-Programs, papers, notes
      - 1937 (Box 28)
      - 1948-1951, 5 folders (Box 28)
      - 1953, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - 1958-1960, 4 folders (Box 28)
      - 1963-1965, 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Executive Committee Minutes
      - 1953 (Box 28)
      - 1958 (Box 28)
      - 1961 (Box 28)
      - 1962 (Box 28)
      - 1963 (Box 29)
      - 1964 (Box 29)
      - 1967 (Box 29)
    - Board of Officers Minutes
      - 1941 (Box 29)
      - 1947 (Box 29)
      - 1952-1955 (Box 29)
      - 1962 (Box 29)
      - 1964, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - 1965 (Box 29)
      - 1966 (Box 29)
    - State and Provincial Section Reports (Box 29)
    - Field Service Division annual report 1963 (Box 29)
    - Subcommittee on Cooperation, Attorney General's Conference on Organized Crime, report 1950 (Box 29)
    - Legislative Committee 1951-1962 (Box 29)
    - International Relations Committee meeting 1951 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous reports 1941 (Box 29)
    - Radio Committee
      - 1932 (Box 29)
      - 1936 (Box 29)
      - 1937 (Box 29)
      - 1939-1941 (Box 29)
      - 1944, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 29)
      - 1948 (Box 29)
      - 1949-1951 (Box 29)
    - Communications Committee 1954-1963 (Box 29)
    - Printed Material (Box 29)
  - Michigan Association of Chiefs of Police 1928-1966
    - Constitution (Box 29)
    - Amendments to constitution (Box 29)
    - Membership lists 1929-1935, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous lists (Box 29)
    - Convention Files
      - Correspondence 1929 (Box 30)
      - Proceedings 1929 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence 1930 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence 1931 (Box 30)
      - Proceedings 1931 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence 1932 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence 1933 (Box 30)
      - Proceedings 1933 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence 1934-1935, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Proceedings 1947-1952 (Box 30)
      - Reports 1961-1965 (Box 30)
    - Convention programs 1924-1943, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Resolutions 1932-1935, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Executive Committee papers 1930-1935, 1938-1963, 7 folders (Box 30)
    - Committee to Cooperate with the State Crime Commission 1929-1930 (Box 30)
    - Police Officers Training School 1929-1936 (Box 30)
    - Police Training Committee 1951-1963 (Box 30)
    - Legislative memorandum 1963-1966, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Correspondence 1928-1937, 8 folders (Box 30)
  - Associated Police Communications Officers 1935-1950
    - Constitution (Box 30)
    - Recommendations for police radio (Box 30)
    - Bulletins 1936-1937, undated, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Correspondence 1935-1939 (Box 30)
    - Conferences
      - 1935-1938 (Box 30)
      - 1944, 3 folders (Box 30)
      - 1950 (Box 30)
  - Permanent Legislative Committee 1944-1963
    - Minutes and reports